

Valeria Zaitseva

UI / UX Designer

About Me

As a designer I have a hands-on approach, with an eye for elegant and joyous visual solutions, coupled with a clear and intuitive navigational structure.

My background in philosophy makes me a strong analytical thinker and my background in sociology drives my passion for user-centered and inclusive design.

Skills and Tools

User Research
Wireframing & Prototyping
Usability Testing
Visual Design
Illustration, Icon & Logo Design
Basic HTML / CSS, Javascript
Russian, German

Sketch, Figma, Adobe XD inVision
Flinto
Miro, Slack, Trello,
Procreate

Work Experience

UI Designer Freelance	Current
Translator Freelance	2018-20
Student Assistant, Tutor for applied Ethics Humboldt-University of Berlin, Department of Philosophy	2016-18
Student Assitant, Tutor for theoretical Philosophy University of Erlangen-Nuremberg, Department of Philosophy	2014-15

Education

CareerFoundry, Online

UI Design Program

Designers	
Humboldt University of Berlin Global Studies, Philosophy Concentration: Epistemology, Identity and the Self, Gender	2015-20
University of Erlangen- Nuremberg Philosophy, B.A. Concentration: Global Justice	2011-15
Sociology, B.A. Concentration: Practice Theory, Ethnomethodology	
Pace University, New York Economics Philosophy	2007-09

2020-21

Get in Touch

Email: zaitseva.v.a@gmail.com

Portfolio: behance.net/

valeriazaitseva2

Profile: https://www.linkedin.com/in/

valeria-zaitseva-587220204/